twibes.com 2015-12-07

# Twibes Twitter Groups

Privacy Statement

Twibes has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitmentto privacy.

Twibes requires access to users' Twitter accounts solely for the following purposes:

  * To allow members to view who they follow and vote for their favorites.
  * To allow members to view voting results, and verify the groups they belong to.
  * To notify those that have been voted for via either a tweet or a direct message
  * To verify members’ identities as group members

Please note: We will never send a direct message or tweet on your behalf without your permission.

We collect personal information in a number of ways when you visit our Site. At several places on our Site, we may collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us which may contain personal information.  Personal information may also be collected if you provide such information in connection with creating a profile, leaving comments, inviting a friend, sending an email or message to another user or participating in any interactive forums or features on the site.  In addition, from time to time we may collect demographic, contact or other personal information you provide in connection with your participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities on the Site.

When you visit our web site, some information is also automatically collected, such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and the time and date of your visit and purchases. We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

We use customer contact information to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and shared with other companies who  may want to contact our visitors. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers are collected to verify the user's identity and for other purposes. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

This site contains links to other sites. Twibes is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

 **Public Forums** The Site may make message boards or discussion lists available to its users. Please remember that any informationthat is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise cautionwhen deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Security** The Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Twibes will employ industry-standard security and disaster-recovery procedures to protect the data. Twibes will perform frequent backups and will store backup materials in a safe and secure environment.

 **Choice/Opt-Out** Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications fromour partners.  This option is provided during the registration sign-in form,and can be modified at any time by the user.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send email to [adam@twibes.com](mailto:adamloving@twibes.com)

 **Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [adam@twibes.com](mailto:adam@twibes.com)

Twibes is not affilliated with Twitter
